[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '走ります' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はしります"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '跳びます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とびます"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '登ります' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "のぼります"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '振ります' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ふります"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '潜ります' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "もぐります"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '押します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おします"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '叩きます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たたきます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '転びます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ころびます"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '投げます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "なげます"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '持ち上げます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "もちあげます"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '振り向きます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ふりむきます"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the kanji '逆立ちます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "さかだちます"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the kanji '逆' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ぎゃく"
    }
]